<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>tetzle.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb_NO">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk_UA">Tetzle</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh">Tetzle</name>
  <summary>Jigsaw puzzle with tetromino pieces</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Trencaclosques Jigsaw amb peces de tetròmino</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Skládanka s díly ve tvaru tetromina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Puzzlespiel mit Tetromino-Puzzleteilen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Παζλ με κομμάτια tetromino</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Puzzle con piezas tetromino</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Dėlionė su tetromino figūromis</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Teka-teki susun suai gambar dengan cebisan tetromino</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb_NO">Puslespill med tetromino-brikker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Legpuzzel met tetrominostukken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra puzzle z części o kształcie tetromina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um quebra-cabeça com peças tetraminós</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Quebra-cabeças com peças em formato de tetris</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Joc puzzle cu piese teromino</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Игра-головоломка с тетрамино</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Tetris benzeri parçalı bir yap-boz oyunu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Головоломка з шматочками тетраміно </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk_UA">Головоломка з шматочками тетроміно</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Tetzle is a jigsaw puzzle game that uses tetrominoes for the pieces. Any image can be imported and used to create puzzles with a wide range of sizes. Games are saved automatically, and you can select between currently in progress games.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Tetzle és un trencaclosques jigsaw que fa servir tetròminos com a peces. Qualsevol imatge pot ésser importada i feta servir per a generar un trencaclosques de un ample ventall de tamany. Els jocs es desan automàticament i es poden tornar a carregar seleccionant un d'entre tots els disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Tetzle ist ein Puzzlespiel mit Tetromino-Puzzleteilen. Beliebige Bilder können importiert werden, um Puzzles verschiedener Größe zu erzeugen. Spiele werden automatisch gespeichert und Sie können zwischen mehreren aktiven Spielen wechseln.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Tetzle είναι ένα παιχνίδι παζλ που χρησιμοποιεί tetromino για κομμάτια. Κάθε εικόνα μπορεί να εισαχθεί και να χρησιμοποιηθεί για δημιουργία παζλ με ένα ευρύ φάσμα μεγεθών. Τα παιχνίδια αποθηκεύονται αυτόματα, και μπορείτε να επιλέξετε ανάμεσα σε εξέλιγμένα παιχνίδια</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Tetzle yra dėlionės žaidimas, kuris naudoja tetromino figūras. Bet kuris paveikslas gali būti importuotas ir naudojamas įvairių dydžių dėlionei sukurti. Žaidimai yra automatiškai įrašomi, ir galima rinktis iš šiuo metu žaidžiamų žaidimų. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Tetzle merupakan permainan teka-teki susun suai gambar yang menggunakan tetromino sebagai cebisannya. Mana-mana imej boleh diimport dan digunakan untuk menghasilkan teka-teki dengan pelbagai julat saiz. Permainan disimpan secara automatik, dan anda boleh pilih permainan yang sedang dimainkan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb_NO">Tetzle er et puslespill som bruker tetromino-brukker. Ethvert bilde kan importeres og brukes til å opprette puslespill i mange forskjellige størrelser. Spill lagres automatisk, og du kan velge mellom spill som er underveis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tetzle is een legpuzzel spel met tetromino als stukken. Elke afbeelding kan worden geïmporteerd en gebruikt om puzzels van verschillende maten mee te maken. De spellen worden automatisch opgeslagen en je kunt tussen actieve spellen schakelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Tetzle to gra puzzle, która składa się z części o kształcie tetromina. Możesz importować każdy obraz i użyć go do tworzenia puzzli w rożnych rozmiarach. Gry są zapisywane automatycznie i możesz wybrać obecne postępy w grach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Tetzle é um jogo de quebra-cabeça que usa tetraminós como peças. Pode ser importada e utilizada qualquer imagem nos quebra-cabeças com uma vasta gama de tamanhos. Os jogos são gravados automaticamente e podem-se selecionar entre vários jogos gravados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Tetzle este un joc de puzzle care utilizează tetromino pentru piesel. Orice imagine poate fi importată şi utilizată pentru a crea puzzle-uri cu o gamă largă de dimensiuni. Jocurile sînt salvate automat, şi puteţi alege între jocrile curente şi în progres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Tetzle - игра-головоломка с тетрамино. Любое изображение может быть загружено и разбито на паззлы с различными настройками размера паззла. Игры сохраняются автоматически, и вы можете выбирать между ними.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Tetzle tetrominoes parçaları kullanan bir bir parçalı bulmaca oyunudur. Herhangi bir görüntü içe aktarılabilir ve çok çeşitli boyutlarda bulmacalar oluşturmak için kullanılabilir. Oyunlar otomatik olarak kaydedilir ve şu anda devam etmekte olan oyunlar arasından seçim yapabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Tetzle - це гра-головоломка, яка використовує тетраміно для шматочків. Будь-яке зображення можна імпортувати та використовувати для створення головоломок із широким діапазоном розмірів. Ігри зберігаються автоматично, і ви можете вибирати між іграми, що тривають. </p>
    <p xml:lang="uk_UA">Tetzle - це гра-головоломка, яка використовує тетроміно для шматочків. Будь-яке зображення можна імпортувати та використовувати для створення головоломок із широким діапазоном розмірів. Ігри зберігаються автоматично, і ви можете вибирати між іграми, які зараз виконуються.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/tetzle/screenshots/appdata.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/tetzle/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/tetzle/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/gottcode/tetzle/</url>

  <developer id="org.gottcode">
    <name translatable="no">Graeme Gott</name>
  </developer>
  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <provides>
    <binary>tetzle</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">tetzle.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">tetzle</icon>

  <categories>
    <category>Game</category>
    <category>LogicGame</category>
  </categories>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>

  <releases>
    <release version="3.0.1" date="2025-01-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Dutch, German, Lithuanian, Romanian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0.0" date="2024-08-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added scrolling at window edges</li>
          <li>Added removing multiple images at once</li>
          <li>Added centering on cursor when zooming</li>
          <li>Improved layout of new game tab</li>
          <li>Improved layout of statusbar</li>
          <li>Replaced OpenGL rendering with QPainter</li>
          <li>Refactored code</li>
          <li>Use native icons in Windows</li>
          <li>Updated AppData</li>
          <li>FIXED: Overview did not stay hidden when closed</li>
          <li>FIXED: Sometimes added image had preview of removed image</li>
          <li>FIXED: Removing an image did not remove its details</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Dutch, German, Lithuanian, Romanian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.2.3" date="2024-01-16">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.2.2" date="2023-01-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added portable mode</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Esperanto, Romanian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.2.1" date="2022-05-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Switched to Qt 6</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Dutch, German, Lithuanian, Ukrainian, Ukrainian (Ukraine)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.2.0" date="2021-09-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added support for Qt 6</li>
          <li>Refactored code</li>
          <li>Removed XPM icon</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Dutch, Turkish, Ukrainian, Ukrainian (Ukraine)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.1.6" date="2020-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Did not load locales with underscores</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.1.5" date="2019-08-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.1.4" date="2019-03-25">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Automatic high DPI support</li>
          <li>FIXED: Unsigned integer conversion warnings in graphics layer</li>
          <li>FIXED: Could not add images with Qt 5.12</li>
          <li>FIXED: Window icon didn't work in Wayland</li>
          <li>Added support for OpenGL ES</li>
          <li>Improved loading locales</li>
          <li>Require Qt 5.9</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Polish</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.1.3" date="2018-05-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Replaced jhead with image auto-rotation in Qt 5.5</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Extra warnings only shown in debug build</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Improved macOS deployment</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Catalan, Chinese, Dutch, Greek, Norwegian Bokmål, Portuguese, Spanish</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
